ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files
1977-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Fleron, Lou Jean
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4283/001
35.5 cubic feet
35.5 linear ft.
Records.
9250168
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 21, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
Arrangement
Series A: UAW-Ford
Series B: UAW-GM
Series C: Utilities
Series D: USWA Copper and Brass
Series E: Telecommunications
Series F: Arts and Entertainment
Series G: Workplace, Industry and Economic Development (WIED)
Series H: Champions at Work Study
Series I: Regional Economic Development
Series J: Empire State Poll (ESP) and Regional Development
Series K: Early Childhood Education Project
Series L: Miscellaneous Programs
Series M: Union Work
Series N: Western Region Administration
Series O: ILR Extension Administration
Series P: Westerr European Organization of te Metal Trades (WEM)
Series Q: Corning Glass
Fleron, Lou Jean; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension and Public Service Division; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
9250168
- Series A: UAW-Ford
  - Ford 897 Program Evaluation, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Nelson's Policy Materials, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ford Policy Materials Report Card, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - UAW Ford Joint Programs Key Documents, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ford UAW Local 897 (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ford UAW Local 897 (Folder 2 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mary Pisnar - Cleveland State, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ford Policy - Transparencies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    Graphs
  - Ford Project Operations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Joe LoGalbo, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    UAW Co-Chairperson
  - Ford - Public Policy, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ford Body and Assembly Operations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ford National Project (Folder 1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ford National Project (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ford Meeting Notes (Folder1 of 2) January 5, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ford Meeting Notes (Folder 2 of 2) January 5, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ford - UAW. March 5, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ford Meeting Notes July 20, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ford Meeting Notes August 13, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ford Meeting Notes September 14, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ford - Other Sections, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Articles for UAW Ford - Monday, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AIS Instructor Manual, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ford Work Current (Folder 1 of 3), 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ford Work Current (Folder 2 of 3), 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ford Work Current (Folder 3 of 3), 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ford Meeting Notes January 11, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Planning Comm. - Evaluation Form Quimby, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ford Current - Mon., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - AIS Program Instruction Guide, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ford Instruction Manual - Monday, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Leadership Proposals, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    News Articles
  - UAW Ford Leadership Conference, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Promo Project, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    35 mm slides
  - AIS Program Response, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - UAW - Ford Many Faces Looking Forward (Folder 1 of 5), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - UAW - Ford Many Faces Looking Forward (2 of 5), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - UAW - Ford Many Faces Looking Forward (3 of 5), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - UAW - Ford Many Faces Looking Forward (Folder 4 of 5), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - UAW - Ford Many Faces Looking Forward (Folder 5 of 5), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ford Revisions, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Automotive Industry Studies Evaluations (Folder 1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Automotive Industry Studies Evaluations (Folder 2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ford AIS Geographical Pilot Program April 29 - May 2, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - UAW - Ford AIS Manual Notes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - UAW - Ford AIS Manual Draft Packs, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - UAW Ford Leadership, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AIS Manual Draft, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - UAW - Ford Automotive Industry Studies Geographical Pilot Program, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - UAW - Ford, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ford Meeting Notes June 7, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - AIS Update, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - UAW Ford Computer Game, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Ford Spring, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - UAW - Ford Jul 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SRPP Ford - UAW, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ford Meeting Notes June 7, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Time of Our Life Revisions December 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AIS - Revisions December 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Time Magazine Special Edition
  - UAW - Ford AIS, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - AIS Evaluations, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ford Sexual Harassment, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Betty Friedan - New Paradigm Project, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - AIS Survey Reports, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - AIS Evaluations, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - AIS Program Intro. Ford Info., 2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - AIS 2000 Revision (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - UAW Ford People of the World, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - AIS - 2000 Update (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Auto - Environment Information, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AIS - Monday, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ford Meeting Notes August 28, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - UAW - Ford Adm. November 2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - AIS Intro. December 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - UAW - Ford - 2001 Work (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UAW - Ford Alternative Energy, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - AIS CD Project, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - UAW - Ford CD, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Picture
  - Technology Review Articles, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - AIS Evaluations, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Time of Our Life Materials for CD-ROM (Folder 1 of 2), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Time of Our Life Material for CD-ROM (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Powering the Planet, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Presentation
  - AIS CD, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - AIS Evaluations, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - AIS 100th Program, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - AIS Evaluations, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hydrogen Fueled Vehicle, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AIS, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - AIS 2004 Programs (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - UAW - Ford Quality Program, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - AIS Manual Revision, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - AIS, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - AIS Applications, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - AIS - Intro. & TOL, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - UAW - Ford Action America (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - UAW - Ford Action America (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - TOL, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - AIS, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - AIS 2005 - Intro. & TOL (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Auto Industry in Transition, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - UAW - Ford Fights Back, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Special Issue of OnEarth
  - AIS, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Series B: UAW-GM
  - Auto Industry - Lab. Rel. (Folder 1 of 2), 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Auto Industry - Lab. Rel. (Folder 2 of 2), 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Notes on my sessions - from N.D.H. - 846, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Auto Industry - Lab. Rel., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - UAW Local 846, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hydra-matic PEL Notes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - National PEL - Boston July 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hydramatic, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - UAW -GM - HRC, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    PEL Information Guide
  - UAW - GM Local PEL Programs, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Local PEL Outline, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rochester Products - 1097, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Magazine
  - RPD - Fall 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Saginaw - Fall 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Saginaw Buffalo Economics, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Saginaw 424 Administration, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Saginaw - 424 - General Materials, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Rochester Products - 1097 Week 1, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Saginaw - 424 Week 1, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Saginaw - 424 Week 2, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Saginaw - 424 Week 2, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Rock Wagner - UAW 686, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Articles (& comments) from Rice, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Saginaw PEL Participants, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Saginaw Survey (Folder 1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Saginaw Survey (Folder 2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sioux City RPD, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - IUE - 6M Dayton, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Materials for Meeting March 31, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Auto Supplies, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    OEM Documents
  - Hydra-matic Division - Hugentobler, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Saginaw Michigan PEL, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Saginaw - Survey Suggestions & Original Ideas, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - S. Survey - Preliminary Report, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Study Design & Analysis, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Saginaw Survey, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Previous Rough Draft, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Most Recent Rough Draft, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Saginaw Survey Final Draft, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Work in America, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - HRC Local PEL Coord.'s, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Regional PEL, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Saginaw PEL Info. (Folder 1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Saginaw PEL Info. (Folder 2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dayton - College Proposals, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Region 9 II, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Saginaw Overheads, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - PEL Materials for HRC, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Work in America, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - C.P.C. - Tonawanda Engine, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dayton January 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - National HRC Local PEL Conference Chicago April 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Harrison - Local 686, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - HRC - Government & Politics, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - HRC PEL, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - HRC, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Instructor Exercises, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Local PEL Session on Governmental Process: Congressional Decision Making Simulation (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - HRC - Cost Information, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Quality Workshop Evaluation Forms October 1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Quality Workshop Evaluation Forms November, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Quality Workshop Evaluation Forms December, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - AAM - UAW - IAM Rosemary's Materials, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - UAW - HM PEL, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - GM - UAW 774 Partial Procedure, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Quality: Working in the Auto Industry II, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Quality Basics - American Axle, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - American Axle UAW, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Quality: Working - Evaluation, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - AAM - Communication, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - American Axle UAW - IAM Quality, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - PELS, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Career to Community - AAM - UAW, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - AAW - UAW "Phase II", 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Russ Eckel, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - American Axle - UAW 424, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - American Axle - UAW- Local 424, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Overheads (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Auto Industry in Transition (General) (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Series C: Utilities
  - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI) Seminar Fall 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Electric Utility Industry Articles (Folder 1 of 2), 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Electric Utility Industry Articles (Folder 2 of 2), 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Electric Utility Industry Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Electrical Utilities Industry, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Impact of Restructuring on Customers (includes ECON info.), 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Information Technology, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Energy Workshop: Understanding the Dynamics of Changing Industry September 9, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Deregulation - Outlook & Market Response, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Federal Policy Initiative (Comprehensive Electricity Competition Plan - CECP), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Generation Plant Divestiture, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Deregulation Abroad, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Customer Service, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Utility Industry Articles (Folder 1 of 3), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Utility Industry Articles (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Utility Industry Articles (Folder 3 of 3), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Consumer Interest Groups (ECON, TURN, UCAN), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Demand Side Management (DSM), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Deregulation - Canada & U.S. - Canada Relations, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Electric Deregulation Overview, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Electric Power Statistics, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Electric Utility Competition/ Restructuring Issues - from EEI, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Energy Efficiency, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Impact of Deregulation on Stock Prices & Investments, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Midwest Power Crisis, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - New York State Utilities, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Outcomes - Pilot Project, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Stranded Costs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Utility Company Rankings, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Utility Deregulation WNYTDC Seminar April 15, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Electric Industry: Miscellaneous Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Electric Industry, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - HR 2335, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - S-740, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Deregulation, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Investment Abroad (U.S. Investments), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Power for Jobs, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - World of Change, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - World of Change - Overheads, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Electric Industry Sr. Thesis by Bridget O'Brien, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Mining Hidden Assets Seminar Materials, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Presentation and pictures
  - Mining Hidden Assets Seminar Materials (Copy 2), 2005 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Energy Articles, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - NRG-IBEW, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Overview of the Electric Industry (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Allegheny Power, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Boston Edison, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Central Maine Power, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - First Energy, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - GPU, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Nipsco, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Oglethorpe, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Ohio Edison, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - PG & E (Pacific Gas & Electric), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - PacifiCorp, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Potomac Electric Power Co. (PEPCO), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Texas Utilities, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Tucson Electric Power (TEP), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Union Electric/ Ameren, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Wisconsin Energy, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Taking Charge (Folder 1 of 6), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Taking Charge (Folder 2 of 6), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Taking Charge (Folder 3 of 6), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Taking Charge (Folder 4 of 6), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Taking Charge (5 of 6), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Taking Charge (Folder 6 of 6), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Niagara Mohawk, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Niagara Mohawk & Dunkirk Steam Station (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Niagara Mohawk & Dunkirk Steam Station (Folder 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Niagara Mohawk, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Niagara Mohawk, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Niagara Mohawk Correspondence and Notes (Folder 1 of 4), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Niagara Mohawk Correspondence and Notes (Folder 2 of 4), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Niagara Mohawk Correspondence and Notes (Folder 3 of 4), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Niagara Mohawk Correspondence and Notes (Folder 4 of 4), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Niagara Mohawk Current Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Niagara Mohawk: Large Commercial and Industrial Customers, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Niagara Mohawk Now., 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Niagara Mohawk: Industry Experts, Contracts, and Sources of Information, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Niagara Mohawk: Taking Charge, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Information Packet
  - Niagara Mohawk Overheads (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Projector Overheads
  - Niagara Mohawk Overheads (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Niagara Mohawk Follow-Up (Folder 1 of 3), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Maps
  - Niagara Mohawk Follow-Up (Folder 2 of 3), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Photographs, Color Presentation
  - Niagara Mohawk Follow-Up (Folder 3 of 3), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Niagara Mohawk: Work of Change Graphics (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Series D: USWA Copper and Brass
  - Fred Smith, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Copper & Brass Industry, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Maps, Graphs
  - Strategies, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Current, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - OAB (Outokumpu American Brass), Evaluations, Etc., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Import & Export Data for Copper, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - North American Competitors, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Hussey Copper Ltd., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Great Lakes Metal Corp., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - PMX Industries, Inc., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Olin (Folder 1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - PMX Industries, Inc., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Olin (Folder 2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Olin (Folder 1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Olin (Folder 2 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Other Competitors, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    CBSA Guide
  - Other Competitors, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Industry Analysis, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Industry Analysis, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Library Notes (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Copper Development Assoc. Inc. Publication List, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Brass Valley Video (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Brass Mill Shipments, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Economic Activity - U.S.A, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Economy - International (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Industry Financial Data (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Employment - Productivity (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Executive Pay, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Wall Street Journal
  - Foreign Labor Trends, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Non Ferrous Metal Data for 1993, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Resources Industry Studies, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Copper Prices, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Paycheck Money Matters - Articles (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Business Money Matters - Articles, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Making it Tomorrow - Articles, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Economics of Our Life Articles, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - American Metal Market - Articles & References, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NAFTA & GATT, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Missions (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "It's You Business" Manual Notes (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Outokumpu Corporate Communications (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Outokumpu Information from External Sources (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Econ Data - International - from Pam H., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - OAB - General, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - From OAB/USWA, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Union Vision, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Instructors, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - OAB Vision, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Employment - Hours, Wages & Industry Contracts (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - U.S.A. Union Membership & Wages (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Employment - Levels, Occupation & Distribution (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Copper & Brass Use in Automobiles (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Copper & Brass Use in Coins (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Copper & Brass Use in Plumbing (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Copper Development Assoc. Usage Intensity (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Copper & Brass Used Others (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Construction - Rates & Characteristics (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Labor Relations & Practices - Various Articles (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Outokumpu American Brass (Box 11, Folder 27)
    OAB Informational Packet
  - Profile Outokumpu in U.S.A/Copper/World (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Various OAB issued information
  - History of Local 593 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Auto Industry History (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - New Industrial Leadership (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Masters: The Brass and Copper Industry (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Outokumpu Mission Statement Outokumpu Mission Statement (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Lou Jean - Globalization Layout (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Charts (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Who is Us, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - "Who is Them?" Robert Reich Harvard Business Review, March/April 1991 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Time Line Cards (Box 11, Folder 38)
    Notecards
  - The Steel Industry Case Study (2 copies) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - OAB Manual Notes (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Outokumpu American Brass Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Lou Jean's Information & New Masters for her Section (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Outokumpu American Brass Industry Education Program (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Lou Jean - Econ Performance (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Technology Review (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - U.S. Manufacturing (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - OAB Industry Education Program (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Brass Revisions (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - The World Economy (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Auto Industry Case Study (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - The Brass and Copper Industry (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Anaconda (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Copper and Brass Articles (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Assessing the Ai Conditioning Market's Demand for Copper Tube, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Assessing the U.S. Automotive Radiator Market's Demand for Copper/Brass, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Lou Jean Fleuron's Presentation (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Lou Jean Fleuron's Presentation (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Brass Industry in the United States, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AB - 593 Materials Kit 1 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AB - 593 Materials Kit 1 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 5)